

YULIANTI

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yulianti-suhanda-49534480

Address: Jl. BB Cipinang Muara II RT 14/04 No. 23, Jatinegara, Jakarta Timur

SUMMARY

I have studied in Krisnadwipayana University for 3,5 years majoring Human Resource Management, faculty of Economy. I had worked at Glaxo Smith Kline Indonesia as market access officer. I consider myself as someone who is self-motivated, detail oriented, have good interpersonal and communication skills, I am also able to work as a part of a team.

WORK HISTORY

Dec 2018 - Until Now

Freelance

Gymnastics Instructor at Sanggar Cipinang (only Weekend)

May 2014 - Dec 2018

Marketing Support Officer & Market Access Officer

PT. Glaxo Smith Kline Indonesia (GSK)

Marketing Support Officer, responsible for Handle all marketing activities (doc event), create submission of financial proses (CERPS System) BAR for event (symposium, stand alone, booth), handle purchase request and purchase order for flight tickets & hotel arrangement HCP. Market Access Officer, responsible for Accept and approve manual order transaction for JKN from JKN Provider, assure that the manual order of provider is correct (in price, volume & region), submit to the approved manual APL order, make summary on a monthly basis, maintain relationship with sales office

Jul 2013 - Oct 2013

Administration Staff

PT. Glaxo Smith Kline Indonesia (GSK) Responsible for office administration, such as data entry: filing documents, correspondences, handled incoming/outgoing letters

Apr 2012 - Mar 2013

Finance Staff

PT. NP Foods Indonesia
Handle account receivable,
account payable, invoices, data
entry

Apr 2010 – Apr 2012

Administration Production Staff

PT. Yamaha Motor MFG West Java Responsible for office administration, such as production report, data entry, filling documents

Education

Formal	Bachelor Degree of Economy Krisnadwipayana University GPA 3,60 out of 4,00 SMKN 46 Jakarta
2009 - 2013	
2006 - 2009	
2003 - 2006	SMPN 25 Jakarta
1997 - 2003	SDN 16 Jakarta
Informal	
2009	Vocational Competencies at SMKN 46
2008 - 2009	Learning course at Nurul Fikri
2007 - 2008	Computer & Internet course at SMKN 46

SKILLS

Presentation	••••
Administration	•••••
Negotiation	•••••
Ms. Office	•••••
Teamwork	•••••
Leadershin	

INTEREST

Travelling, Social Activity, Environment, Event Organizing, Reading, Administration, Meet and communicate with many people, Dancing